indopia.in 2010-02-25

# Indiareport.com,India entertainment News,Indian Politics News,Latest Sports News,Top Breaking News,India

Indiareport.com and India Report.LLC are licensees of the TRUSTe privacy program and TRUSTe Children’s Privacy Program and are in compliance with TRUSTe privacy principles. We also participate in the Council of Better Business Bureaus' BBBOnLine Privacy Program, and comply with all BBBOnLine Privacy standards. 

This policy discloses the privacy practices for Indiareport.com and India Report, LLC Learning Network. For further information, please also visit our Member Center, where under the Site Help tab, you can view our Member Agreement and read Frequently Asked Questions about Cookies. In the Member Center you can also review Your Profile as well as manage your E-mail Preferences. By using Indiareport.com you are agreeing to the terms of our Member Agreement. 

 TRUSTe 

When you visit a Web site displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, you can expect to be notified of what personally identifiable information of yours is collected; what organization is collecting the information; how the information is used; with whom the information may be shared; what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; what kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company’s control; and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Privacy Policy at Indiareport.com if the Web site has not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact TRUSTe. 

 BBBOnLine 

A wholly owned subsidiary of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, BBBOnLine's mission is to promote trust and confidence on the Internet through the BBBOnLine Reliability and the BBBOnLine Privacy programs. Launched in March 1999, BBBOnLine Privacy awards seals to online businesses that have been verified to be following good information practices. Further information about this program is available at <http://www.bbbonline.org/>

India Report, LLC and Indiareport.com have adopted a set of information management guidelines which serve as the basis for our customer and advertiser relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If the changes represent a material departure from our current practices with respect to the use of personal information, the changes will be posted on this page thirty days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via e-mail. 

Indiareport.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link. 

In this Privacy Policy, you will find the answers to the following questions:

**What information does Indiareport.com gather/track about you?**

Registration: During a free registration process prior to using the site, Indiareport.com requires that you supply a unique Member ID, e-mail address, and demographic information (country, zip code, year of birth, gender, household income, industry, and job title). You must agree to the terms of our Member Agreement. 

Premium Products and Services from Third Parties or Partners: From time to time, Indiareport.com may offer products or services from our partners or third parties. Where you are so notified during the purchase process, the information you provided at registration may be shared with the provider of the product or service. However, we will never share your billing and credit card information, which Indiareport.com collects and stores to enable the purchase of these products. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction. Examples of this include fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments. 

Contests, Special Offers, Surveys: On occasion, Indiareport.com also collects additional personal information from subscribers in connection with optional contests or optional special offers. If this information is to be shared with a third party, we will notify you at the time of collection. 

Additionally, Indiareport.com may collect additional personal information from subscribers in connection with optional surveys. Information that you provide in answer to optional survey questions may be shared, but only in the aggregate, with advertisers and partners unless we notify you at the time of collection. 

IP Addresses: Indiareport.com logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behavior on our site. 

Log Files: _Log data is only used in aggregate to analyze usage of our Web site._

back to top

**What does Indiareport.com do with the information it gathers/tracks?**

Statistical Analysis and Banner Advertising: Indiareport.com may perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site (for product development purposes) and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen or "clicked" their advertising banners. We also use demographic and preference information to allow advertising banners on our Web site to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means that users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads. In this statistical analyses and banner advertisement targeting, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. Indiareport.com may also share personal information with Boleeto.tv and Visipass.com, including analysis to improve customer relationships. Personal information about you as an individual subscriber will not be provided to any third party without your consent, except under the circumstances described in Compliance with Legal Process below. 

_**E-Mail:**_ If you so elect at registration or in the E-mail Preferences section of our Member Center, Indiareport.com will periodically send you promotional e-mail about services offered by Indiareport.com and its advertisers. Additionally, the e-mail address provided by you at registration may be used by Indiareport.com and India Report, LLC to contact you regarding (1) account status (including confirmation of registration), (2) major changes to the Web site and or to the Member Agreement and Privacy Policy, and (3) participation in user surveys, asking for feedback on the Web site and existing or prospective products and services, as well as information to better understand our users. User surveys greatly help us to improve our Web site, and any information we obtain in such surveys will not be shared with third parties, except in aggregate form. (Effective as of May 1, 2006). 

The E-Mail This Article feature is an easy way for Indiareport.com users to send articles through e-mail. The e-mail address(es) that you supply to use this service will only be used to send the requested article. 

We use e-mail links located in the Site Help area our Member Center to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We will use your e-mail address to respond directly to these questions or comments. 

Except as permitted by this policy, Indiareport.com does not send unsolicited e-mail. 

_**Data Security:**_ To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. __

back to top

**With whom does Indiareport.com share the information it gathers/tracks?**

Indiareport.com shares the information it gathers, in aggregate form only, with advertisers and other partners. We will not release personal information about you as an individual to third parties, except under the circumstances described in Compliance with Legal Process below. You can review and modify all of your personal information provided during the free registration process by visiting the secured Your Profile section of our Member Center. If you do not remember your Member ID and password, please go to www.Indiareport.com/forgot for assistance. 

Programs From Our Partners: During the registration process, new users who select to register for certain featured offers from our partners will begin receiving e-mail from these companies. You will only receive e-mail messages from these companies if you elect this opt-in service. In addition to providing these partners with your e-mail address, certain partners may also receive other information collected on the Indiareport.com registration form but this will be noted on the Additional Information page, linked from the Programs from our Partners area of the Registration page. Indiareport.com may use this information as set forth in this privacy policy. Should you decide to discontinue your e-mail subscription or would like more information on these companies, please see our list of partners that have participated in this program. 

Forums and Readers' Reviews: Indiareport.com offers Forums (message boards) and Readers' Reviews. Any information you disclose when posting a message in these areas, along with your Member ID, becomes public and may be used by Indiareport.com for related online and offline promotional uses. For more information about Forums and Readers' Reviews see the Posting Policy and read the Forums, Discussions and Readers' Reviews section of the Member Agreement. You may also write to the Forums moderators by clicking here. __

back to top

**How do I change or update my personal information?**

The Member Center: The Member Center is a centralized area where you can manage your relationship with Indiareport.com. There are a number of things you can do in the Member Center to ensure your personal information is accurate and up to date. Under the Your Profile tab, you can gain secure access to update the information you provided during the free registration process. The E-mail Preferences tab is the place to go to sign up for our E-mail newsletters and manage your delivery options. In order to gain access to the areas of the Member Center containing personal information, you will be asked to re-enter your password. If you do not remember your password, please go to www.Indiareport.com/forgot for assistance. If you need further assistance, please contact Customer Service. __

back to top

**Compliance with Legal Process**

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Indiareport.com; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions). __

back to top

**Children's Guidelines: The Learning Network  **

The Learning Network is a free service for parents, teachers and students, and does not require registration. The Student Connections section is specifically directed at students, grades 6 to 12; within this section, the Ask Indiareport.com allows students to send a question to Indiareport.com providing their first name, grade, school and state/country and optionally their e-mail address. The information requested on these pages is used solely for participation in these activities, and is not shared or sold to third parties. Access to the above services is not conditioned on more information than is reasonably necessary to provide the services. Because we’re concerned about a Parent’s right to consent to the collection and use of their child’s personal information, when a question is published, only the student's first name, grade, and state/country appear on the site. To request removal of this information (non-personally identifiable) or to review or remove the optional e-mail address (personal information collected), please use this form to contact the Learning Network. 

These Childrens’ guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. In the unlikely event of such changes they will be posted on this page. If the changes represent a material departure from our current practices with respect to the use of children’s personal information, the changes will be posted on this page thirty days prior to taking effect and will not affect children’s personal information previously collected. __

back to top

For any questions concerning The Learning Network, please contact: 

**Indraneel Varma,  
India Report, LLC,   
30 Saratoga Drive, West Windsor, NJ 08550.  
Telephone: 609-529-3108**
